<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Phoenix Real Estate Podcast with Curtis Johnson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Curtis Johnson Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Curtis Johnson</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-08-29 16:06:07 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Curtis Johnson</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Curtis@CurtisJohnsonRealty.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Curtis Johnson</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Phoenix Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Curtis Johnson Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Kind of Training Do We Provide for Our Agents? </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/phoenix-real-estate-agent-why-we.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
          <category>Curtis Johnson</category>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Agent</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-06-18 14:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Why+we+believe+in+continuous+training.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

Real estate agents change brokerages for many reasons, but one reason we see a lot is that a brokerage just didn’t provide enough training for them.

We pride ourselves on the fact that we train essentially every day of the week. On Mondays and Fridays we have a team huddle, and then Tuesday is our big team meeting. On Wednesdays and Thursdays we focus on training our agents with their scripts or how to win a listing, etc.

“We believe in investing in YOU!”

We cover such a large area here in the Valley that we put our training up online for you to access anywhere, at anytime. We believe that training is the key to raising your income, because you are your biggest asset.

I’m part of some different groups that discuss new strategies, and I personally run 90% of the training sessions that we have here. Sometimes I’ll bring in another top producer from around the country to share ideas, and we will also occasionally host a mini-mastermind group.

If you have any questions about our training program or about our brokerage in general, please be sure to reach out to me. I’m always willing to assist you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Why+we+believe+in+continuous+training.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Why+we+believe+in+continuous+training.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Increase the Web Presence of Your Business?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/phoenix-real-estate-agent-coaching.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
          <category>Curtis Johnson</category>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Agent</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-04-02 16:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+The+secret+to+online+lead+generation.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

Hello, and welcome back to our coaching blog! Today, we discuss the importance of maintaining a presence online if you want to grow your business.

Years ago, the internet was basically a glorified Rolodex for real estate agents. TV and radio were the biggest marketing tools, and it was somewhat easy to track how well they were working. Now, just about everyone starts their search online - whether it’s for a car, a new watch, or a home. If your product isn’t found when someone searches for it online, you’re out of the discussion!

Not only is it important to be found - it’s also important to dominate the search engines. Both your branded and unbranded information needs to be easily accessible online if you want to attract both new business and repeat business.

“On our team, we take care of the web presence so that our agents can focus on what they do best.”

One of the benefits of being on a team is the time you have to focus on dollar-producing activities. Sitting around messing with your Facebook page or changing the font for an online ad is not going to result in sales. So you need to ask yourself: what are you doing to drive business in? Our team spends a lot of money to build a website for each member of our team in order to drive leads to them. This helps them convert leads at the highest possible level.

Staying visible online is a very competitive endeavor. Do a search for yourself and see what you find. Do you like what you see? If not, now’s not the time to try to become a web master. On our team, we take care of the web presence so that our agents can focus on what they do best. The web is an ever-changing landscape, and there just isn’t enough time to juggle being a diligent agent and a web guru; that’s why we take that part of the business off our agents’ plates.

If you want to expose your clients’ homes to the most amount of people, you need to syndicate your listings with various websites. We’re very aggressive about this - we have virtual tours, HD tours, 3D tours, and drone videos. The goal is to stand out, be different, and make our content easy to find online. You either do this yourself or you pay for someone to do it for you. One of the benefits of being part of a large team is that they are able to handle that aspect of the business for you.

If you have any questions about maintaining an online presence without sacrificing time and energy that would be better spent with clients, give us a call or shoot us a quick email. We would love to help you grow your business and succeed in real estate!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+The+secret+to+online+lead+generation.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+The+secret+to+online+lead+generation.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Your Real Estate Coaching Questions Answered</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/pheonix-real-estate-agent-coaching-blog.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
          <category>Curtis Johnson</category>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Agent</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-03-30 16:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Real+estate+coaching+advice.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com.

Welcome to my new real estate coaching blog! My goal is to help you to grow your business and reach new levels of success within this industry. If you find something interesting, or have questions about anything discussed here, then please feel free to contact me and to use me as a resource.

How often should you reach out to past clients?
People begin to forget about you 21 days after you speak to them. So, ideally, you should reach out to them about every three weeks with a quick email, text, or phone call. Forming a system to do this is important, and will likely determine your success or failure within this aspect of the business. You don’t need to contact them just about real estate, it can be casual, but just make sure they know that you’re still there.

“If you find something interesting, or have questions about anything discussed here, please feel free to contact me and use me as a resource.”

How much business should come from repeats and referrals?
Most agents can’t market to new businesses because they’re flushed for cash, so in the real world about 80-90% of an agent’s business would be coming from repeats and referrals. Ideally, 40-50% of my business would come from this so I could grow my base of clients, but with growing companies it’s important to utilize referrals and repeat customers.

Will working with an established team help an agent gain new business?
I was 26 when I entered this business and I really didn’t have a lot of value, but when you join an established business you can automatically get a lot of experience. Overall, if you’re starting out in this industry, you need to find something that gives you immediate credibility. People need to trust you, so working with an established team is very helpful within this aspect.

Hopefully this has been valuable to you, and if you have any further questions, please be sure to contact me and I would be more than glad to help you out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Real+estate+coaching+advice.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent+Real+estate+coaching+advice.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How You Can Build Experience in the Phoenix Area</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/phoenix-real-estate-agent-coaching.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
          <category>Curtis Johnson</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-03-25 10:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent-+Should+you+work+with+buyers+or+sellers%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

Hello, and welcome to the Curtis Johnston Realty coaching blog!

We’re going to be coming to you via video every few weeks to give you tips and tricks to help you grow your business! If we cover something here that you find interesting, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. If you want to take an even deeper look at a topic, we highly suggest setting up a strategy session with our team!

Many agents approach us and ask whether they should work with buyers or sellers. To answer that question, the first thing you need to do is ask yourself what outcome you’re looking for. After all, the more specific the outcome you strive for, the more specific your path needs to be. It’s much easier to break into the industry on the buyer’s side because you can often out-friend even top producers. Buyers are looking to buy a home, and sellers are looking for an agent with the right marketing strategy. If you don’t have a large budget or much of a track record, your best bet is to start on the buyer side of things until you start producing at a high level.

“The more specific the outcome you strive for - the more specific your path needs to be.”

Our team is one of the few that helps people specialize in the area that’s best for them. Some people gravitate toward sellers, while others gravitate more toward buyers; some people are able to do both. It all has to do with the personality profile of the person in question. Our system allows for multiple avenues of success for our agents, while most other teams will force you to start on the buyer side.

If this topic interests you, or if you’re wondering what your personality profile is, give us a call or shoot us a quick email. We would love to hear from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent-+Should+you+work+with+buyers+or+sellers%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Phoenix+Real+Estate+Agent-+Should+you+work+with+buyers+or+sellers%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Activities Should I Be Doing to Guarantee Success?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-activities-should-i-be-doing-to.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-02-12 10:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

Thanks for joining us once again. Today we’d like to share with you a question we get quite frequently from agents who are just starting out. Everybody wants to make it in this business, so people keep asking me, “What activities should I be doing to guarantee success?”

“Success leaves clues, and we’ve tracked millions of agents from across the country and boiled their success down to a few key metrics that you can learn a lot from.”

Being a solo agent in the real estate business can be frustrating. We see a lot of value in working in a team environment where you can specialize in one area, but that’s not for everybody. Success leaves clues, and we’ve tracked millions of agents from across the country and boiled their success down to a few key metrics that you can learn a lot from.

One of the best activities you can do to ensure success is practicing the “10-2-1” method in your business each week. This means you are asking for 10 appointments, do 2 home tours with 2 different buyers, and attend 1 listing presentation per week. Sticking to this plan and doing it each week will give you the life that others envy.

Thanks for taking the time to check out our blog. If you want to align your natural ability to your preferences and make more money selling real estate, reach out to us. We’d be glad to help you out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The First Step In Building a Real Estate Team</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-first-step-in-building-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2015-02-03 16:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

Today we want to address a question we get quite frequently. People have started to take notice that the team structure in real estate has made real estate business more profitable than they ever have been. Working in real estate as a team is not a new idea, but where do those who want to start their own team begin? We are here today to answer that question.

Like many things in real estate, people that give advice are usually just spectators. I started building my team 15 years ago and I have seen pretty much everything in the process of selling over 3000 homes.

“Working in real estate as a team is not a new idea, but where do those who want to start their own team begin?”

I started my team like most people, realizing that I had too much on my plate before hiring a buyer specialist to help out. We grew our team through trial and error, and there are a ton of things we wish we would have known beforehand about the business. Here are the two most important takeaways:

1. Make sure you want a team
 Don’t just start a team because somebody tells you to do it, make sure you want a team working with you to sell homes. Although the team structure can be lucrative, it’s not for everyone and definitely not the only way to make money in real estate.

2. Don’t hire before your systems are ready
 Simply hiring someone won’t do any good. You need to have good systems in place for training new employees and bringing them up to speed, so the people you hire can follow it and you can multiply and scale your business.

Hopefully these tips will help you in your journey. If you have any questions, feel free to give us a call or send us a quick email. We are always here to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How the Right Systems Can Bring You 9 Buyers and 9 Sellers in Just 90 Days</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/phoenix-real-estate-recruiting.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Recruiting</category>
        
        <author>Curtis Johnson</author>
        <pubDate>2014-12-15 16:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Curtis+Johnson+Recruiting+Video.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

Phoenix Real Estate Agent

Every day agents wake up wondering, “Where is my next deal coming from?”

Many agents go to bed the same night with that question still unanswered.

The solution seems easy - you just need more leads.

“We can help more agents, who have motivation and potential for great success, by providing a system that gives you more than just leads.”

But the real problem is where those leads come from, and all the stress and uncertainty of not having a consistent source of leads.

Curtis Johnson Realty can eliminate that uncertainty and stress from your life.

The systems, programs, training and support we’ve developed over the years have put us in a unique position.

We can help more agents, who have motivation and potential for great success, by providing a system that gives you more than just leads. We give you the scripts, training and support you need to convert those leads into closings.

And closings are what really count.

See what a couple of our agents have to say about why they joined Curtis Johnson Realty.

Everything I need is here so scripts, leads, especially lead generation is unbelievable. Programs, the splits, leadership, direction, support, everything. Everything you can think of, even things you hadn’t thought of, are here. - Michael Barry

The biggest factor for me was the lead generation, and no other company in the state could offer the lead generation that Curtis Johnson Realty offers. It’s second to none. He spends a lot of money marketing and we generate tons of leads every single day, so you have a lot more opportunities here than anywhere else. - Josh Whittemore

In fact, we believe so strongly in the systems we’ve created that we guarantee you’ll bring in 9 buyers and 9 sellers in 90 days, or we’ll back it up with $9,000 in cash.

If you’re serious about your real estate career, click here for more information on our systems. If you like what you see, the next step is to sit down together, go through your goals and experience and see if Curtis Johnson Realty is a good fit for you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Curtis+Johnson+Recruiting+Video.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Curtis+Johnson/Curtis+Johnson+Recruiting+Video.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Curtis Johnson</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Looking to improve your real estate career? I’m here to help you make a smart decision when it comes to growing your business, improving your bottom line, and choosing a place to work in real estate sales. If you’d like to learn more about working with Curtis Johnson Realty, contact me at 480-355-4055 or email career@curtisjohnsonrealty.com

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Curtis Johnson</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Curtis Johnson</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Curtis Johnson Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
